

UX DESIGNER

MAIN OBJECTIVE

I am a proactive UX Desginer with experience working on mobile apps and websites. I am passionate about implementing efficient and appealing designs for users built on an understanding of technology and collaboration with stakeholders and team members

CONTACT DETAILS

- Cell: 323-895-0712
- alicianunezux@gmail.com
- alicianunez.github.io.
- 1858 S Dunsmuir Ave, Los Angeles CA 90019

DEVELOPMENT

- -HTML/CSS, Javascript, Python
- -React Native, Bootstrap

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Wireframing, Prototyping, Storyboarding, Personas
- Cognitive Walkthroughs, Usability Testing
- Comparative Analysis, Interviews, Surveying

SOFT SKILLS

- -- Proficient Spanish Speaker
- Project Management, Requirements Gathering
- Self Motivated, Problem Solving, Fast Learner
- Active Communication

CERTIFICATE

BCG VIRTUAL EXPERIENCE PROGRAM 2020

- -Participated in the open access BCG Virtual Experience program with Forage,
- Completed Strategic and Experience design modules.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OFFICE MANAGER

Santa Monica Auto Body | 2020 - present

- Managed the front desk and interacted with customers via phone/in-person to provide estimates and assistance.
- Selected and ordered office supplies and auto parts.
- Handled important documents, including finances and city-mandated permits for the shop.

CAST MEMBER

Disneyland Resort | 2017 - 2019

- Provided personable guest service to a diverse guest base, while upholding company-wide standards.
- -Demonstrated strong problem solving skills when confronted with guest requests and ride operation issues.
- Strived to ensure safety and create memorable experiences through guest control and interaction.

PUBLICITY CHAIR

Sigma Delta Sigma | 2018 - 2019

- Managed logistics and event planning for events.
- -Designed flyers using Adobe Photoshop. Advertised events through social media and reached a wide audience.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, IRVINE

BA in Informatics | 2015 - 2020

- Specialized in Human-Computer Interaction.
- Minor in Linguistics.

YONSEI UNIVERSITY

Semester Abroad | 2019

PROJECTS

NEWS X-RAY (FACIAL RECOGNITION MOBILE APP)

University of California, Irvine | 2019

- Designed and implemented an app that identifies political pundits.
- Developed the front-end using React Native.
- Held user testing sessions and engaged in other research methods to better understand our clientele.